{
  
  "title": "Christmas Quiz",
  
  "teams": [
    "He-Elves",
    "She-Elves"
  ],

  "categories": [
    "The Grinch",
    "Christmas Songs",
    "Who Said It",
    "Name That Movie",
    "Misc"
  ],

  "tiles": [
    [
      {
        "id": "1_1",
        "question": "I wouldnâ€™t touch you with this length of pole.",
        "answer": "39 1/2 foot pole"
      },
      {
        "id": "1_2",
        "question": "His heart was how many sizes too small?",
        "answer": "2 Sizes"
      },
      {
        "id": "1_3",
        "question": "He took the last can of...",
        "answer": "Who Hash"
      },
      {
        "id": "1_4",
        "question": "He's as cuddly as this desert flora.",
        "answer": "Cactus"
      },
      {
        "id": "1_5",
        "question": "Where does the Grinch call home?",
        "answer": "My Crumpit"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "id": "2_1",
        "question": "Finish this lyric: \"Make my wish come true...\"",
        "answer": "All I want for Christmas is you."
      },
      {
        "id": "2_2",
        "question": "Given on the 11th day of Christmas",
        "answer": "11 Pipers Piping"
      },
      {
        "id": "2_3",
        "question": "In \"Winter Wonderland\" this bird has gone away.",
        "answer": "Blue Bird"
      },
      {
        "id": "2_4",
        "question": "\"...I'm offering this simple phrase to kids from one to ____\"",
        "answer": "Ninety Two"
      },
      {
        "id": "2_5",
        "question": "\"... Fast away the _____ passes. ... fa-la-la-la-la ...\"",
        "answer": "Old Year"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "id": "3_1",
        "question": "Bah humbug!",
        "answer": "Ebenezer Scrooge"
      },
      {
        "id": "3_2",
        "question": "We elves try to stick to the four main food groups: candy, candy canes, candy corns and syrup.",
        "answer": "Buddy the Elf"
      },
      {
        "id": "3_3",
        "question": "Observe the bumble's one weakness. ... The bumble sinks! Ha ha!",
        "answer": "Yukon Cornelius"
      },
      {
        "id": "3_4",
        "question": "You want the moon? Just say the word and I'll throw a lasso around it and pull it down.",
        "answer": "George Bailey"
      },
      {
        "id": "3_5",
        "question": "Save the neck for me, Clark.",
        "answer": "Cousin Eddie"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "id": "4_1",
        "question": "You'll shoot your eye out kid!",
        "answer": "A Christmas Story"
      },
      {
        "id": "4_2",
        "question": "Strange, isn't it? Each man's life touches so many other lives. When he isn't around he leaves an awful hole, doesn't he?",
        "answer": "TIts a Wonderful Life"
      },
      {
        "id": "4_3",
        "question": "He never got his picture on bubble gum cards, did he? Have you ever seen his picture on a bubble gum card? Hmmm? How can you say someone is great who's never had his picture on bubble gum cards?",
        "answer": "A Charlie Brown Christmas"
      },
      {
        "id": "4_4",
        "question": "Keep the change ya filthy animal.",
        "answer": "Home Alone"
      },
      {
        "id": "4_5",
        "question": "Grace? She passed away 30 years ago!",
        "answer": "Christmas Vacation"
      }
    ],
    [
      {
        "id": "5_1",
        "question": "What did frosty the snowman have for a nose?",
        "answer": "A Button"
      },
      {
        "id": "5_2",
        "question": "How much did Lucy charge for a psychiatric session in the classic \"Christmas TV special A Charlie Brown Christmas\"",
        "answer": "Five Cents"
      },
      {
        "id": "5_3",
        "question": "In the Christmas Classic, It's A Wonderful Life, what happened every time a bell rang?",
        "answer": "An Angel Gets Its Wings"
      },
      {
        "id": "5_4",
        "question": "According to the movie \"The Elf\", the best way to spread christmas cheer is what?",
        "answer": "Singing Loud for All to Hear"
      },
      {
        "id": "5_5",
        "question": "How many gifts would you receive if you received all of the gifts in the song \"The Twelve Days of Christmas\"?",
        "answer": "364"
      }
    ]
  ]
}
